Guide to the Fred Friendly Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Media and Society Seminars, 1974-1996
  - Managing Our Miracles (Box 124)
    - Research Notes and Hypotheticals, 1986 (Box 124, Folder F.1)
    - Promotional Materials and Reviews, 1986 (Box 124, Folder F.2)
    - Production Binder, 1986 (Box 124, Folder F.3)
    - Transcripts
      - Case I: "AIDS: Public Epidemic, Private Tragedy, 1986 April 19 (Box 124, Folder F.4)
      - Case III: "Organ Transplants and the Artificial Heart," 1986 April 20, (2 Folders) (Box 124, Folder F.5-6)
    - Arizona--Hypotheticals, 1980 November 18 (Box 124, Folder F.8)
  - Media and Business Seminars (Box 125)
    - Chicago--Packet, 1979 (Box 125, Folder F.1)
    - Chicago--Transcripts, 1979, (3 Folders) (Box 125, Folder F.2-4)
    - Columbia University--Transcripts, 1981, (3 Folders) (Box 125, Folder F.5-7)
    - Kansas City--Transcripts, 1981 September 18-19 (Box 125, Folder F.8)
  - Media and Business Seminars (Box 126)
    - Michigan--Transcripts, 1980 November 10-11 (Box 126, Folder F.1)
    - Minnesota--Hypotheticals and Program, 1980 June 17-18 (Box 126, Folder F.2)
    - Princeton--Hypotheticals and Transcripts, 1977 October 7-9, (3 Folders) (Box 126, Folder F.3-5)
    - Seattle--Hypotheticals and Transcripts, 1982 June 18-19, (3 Folders) (Box 126, Folder F.6-8)
  - Media and Business Seminars (Box 127)
    - Snowbird Conference--Transcripts, 1982, (3 Folders) (Box 127, Folder F.1-3)
    - Western Conference--Hypotheticals and Program, 1980 February 8-10 (Box 127, Folder F.4)
    - Western Conference--Transcripts, 1980 February 8-10, (3 Folders) (Box 127, Folder F.5-7)
  - Media and Business Seminars (Box 128)
    - Western Conference--Transcripts, 1980 February 8-10 (Box 128, Folder F.1)
  - Conference on Media, Business, and Law --Transcripts, 1978 May 13-14, (4 Folders) (Box 128, Folder F.2-5)
  - The Media and the Family --Program, 1978 (Box 128, Folder F.6)
  - The Media and Government --Transcripts, 1980 March 29-30, (2 Folders) (Box 128, Folder F.7-8)
  - Conference on the Media and City Government-- Transcript, 1980 November 21-23 (Box 129, Folder F.1)
    - New Delhi-- 1978 August 24-27 (Box 129)
    - Sri Lanka-- 1980 February 22-24 (Box 129, Folder F.3)
    - Session Planning Notes, 1977-1986 (Box 129)
    - Conference Programs, 1977-1980 (Box 129, Folder F.5)
    - Akron--Transcripts, 1978 October 28, (2 Folders) (Box 129, Folder F.6-7)
    - Akron--Transcripts, 1978 October 28 (Box 130)
    - Anglo-American Conference on the News and the Law, Kent--Transcripts, 1977 June 25, (4 Folders) (Box 130, Folder F.2-5)
    - ASNE--Hypotheticals, 1977 (Box 130, Folder F.6)
    - Federal Communications Bar, 1978 September 15-16 (Box 130, Folder F.7)
  - Media and the Law (Box 131)
    - Federal Communications Bar--Transcript, 1978 September 15-16 (Box 131, Folder F.1)
    - Jacksonville--Session Planning Notes, 1987 (Box 131, Folder F.2)
    - Judicial Conference of the 8th Circuit--Hypotheticals and Program, 1980 July 6-9 (Box 131, Folder F.3)
    - Metropolitan Conference--Hypotheticals and Program, 1980 May 3 (Box 131, Folder F.4)
    - National Association of Women Judges--Transcript, 1982 October 10 (Box 131, Folder F.5)
    - National Conference--Transcripts, 1977 November 5-6, (4 Folders) (Box 131, Folder F.6-9)
  - Media and the Law (Box 132)
    - New England--Report, 1974 June 7-9 (Box 132, Folder F.1)
    - New York State Judicial Seminar--Transcripts, 1982 August 6, (2 Folders) (Box 132, Folder F.2-3)
    - New York Times--Program, 1977 March 26 (Box 132, Folder F.4)
    - Northern California--Program and Transcripts, 1978 December 8, (4 Folders) (Box 132, Folder F.5-8)
  - Media and the Law (Box 133)
    - Philadelphia--Transcripts, 1978 January 13-15, (2 Folders) (Box 133, Folder 1-2)
    - Rochester--Transcripts, 1978 August 5, (3 Folders) (Box 133, Folder F.3-5)
    - Seattle--Transcript, 1983 April 30 (Box 133, Folder F.6)
  - Media and the Law (Box 134)
    - Seattle--Transcripts, 1983 April 30, (2 Folders) (Box 134, Folder F.1-2)
    - Southern California--Hypotheticals and Program, 1977 February 11-13 (Box 134, Folder F.3)
    - Tennessee--Transcripts, 1978, (2 Folders) (Box 134, Folder F.4-5)
    - Texas--Program, 1979 (Box 134, Folder F.6)
    - Tri-State Regional--Transcripts, 1978 October 14, (2 Folders) (Box 134, Folder F.7-8)
    - Tri-State Regional--Transcripts, 1978 October 14 (Box 135)
    - Washington--Hypotheticals and Program, 1977 August 26-28 (Box 135, Folder F.2)
    - West Virginia--Transcripts, 1976 December 3-5, (2 Folders) (Box 135, Folder F.3-4)
  - The Media, the Law, and the Constitution --Research Notes and Articles, 1988, (2 Folders) (Box 136, Folder F.1-2)
  - Conference on Media and Libel--Program and Transcripts, 1983 May 20-21, (2 Folders) (Box 136, Folder F.3-4)
  - Midwest Conference on Libel, Media, and Business --Transcripts, 1983, (3 Folders) (Box 136, Folder F.5-7)
  - Media Practices and Investigative Reporting --Transcripts, 1981 October 10-11 (Box 137, Folder F.1-2)
  - Media, Terrorism, and Public Order --Hypotheticals and Program, 1980 May 16-18 (Folder F.3)
    - Production Information, 1984 (Box 137)
    - "A Matter of Intelligence"--Transcript, 1984 (Box 137, Folder F.5)
    - "The Correspondent Under Fire"--Transcript, 1984 (Box 137, Folder F.6)
    - Transcripts, 1984, (4 Folders) (Box 138, Folder F.1-4)
    - Research Notes, 1984, (2 Folders) (Box 138, Folder F.5)
    - Research Notes, 1984 (Box 139, Folder F.1)
  - Media, Minorities, and Society --Transcripts, 1981 November 20-21 (Box 139, Folder F.2)
  - Media Practices and Investigative Reporting, 1981 (Box 139, Folder F.3)
  - Medical Ethics Seminar--Transcript, undated (Box 139, Folder F.4)
  - Medical Malpractice Seminar--Transcripts, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 139, Folder F.5-7)
  - Medicine and Society (Folder F.8)
    - Transcripts, 1984 (Box 139)
    - Transcripts, 1984, (6 Folders) (Box 140)
  - Medicine and Society (Box 141)
    - Transcripts, 1984, (3 Folders) (Box 141, Folder F.1-3)
  - Moral Dilemmas of the Presidency --Proposal, 1982 (Box 141, Folder F.4)
  - National Institute of Justice --Seminar Packet, 1994 (Box 141, Folder F.5)
  - National Seminar on the Bill of Rights-- Transcripts, 1982 April 3, (2 Folders) (Box 141, Folder F.6-7)
  - National Seminar on the Bill of Rights --Transcripts, 1982 April 3 (Box 142, Folder F.1)
  - National Seminar on State Courts and Public Policy --Transcripts, 1979, (2 Folders) (Box 142, Folder F.3-4)
  - National Seminar on State Courts and Public Policy --Transcripts, 1979 (Box 143, Folder F.1)
  - New York State Foundation Conference on Crime and Punishment --Planning Materials, 1985 (Box 143, Folder F.2)
  - Nuclear Winter--Proposal, 1984 (Folder F.3)
    - Promotional Materials, 1990 (Box 143)
    - "Athletics and Academics: An Uneasy Alliance"--Research Notes and Transcript, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 143, Folder F.5-6)
    - Brawley Case--Planning Materials, 1988 (Box 143, Folder F.7)
    - "Entertainment News or Entertainment?"--Research Notes and Transcript, 1988, (2 Folders) (Box 143, Folder F.8-9)
  - The Other Side of the News (Box 144)
    - "Television and Terrorism: Who Calls the Shots?"--Planning Materials, 1990 (Box 144, Folder F.1)
    - "Safe Speech, Free Speech, and the Constitution"--Planning Materials, 1991 (Box 144, Folder F.2)
    - "Safe Speech, Free Speech, and the Constitution"--Transcript, 1991, (2 Folders) (Box 144, Folder F.3-4)
  - Popular Culture: Rage, Rights, and Responsibility --Research Notes and Articles, 1992 (Box 144, Folder F.5)
  - Preserving the Independence and Integrity of the Judiciary --Transcripts, 1985, (2 Folders) (Box 144, Folder F.6-7)
  - The President and Congress --Planning Materials and Notes, circa 1986 (Folder F.8)
    - General, 1987 (Box 144)
  - The Presidency and the Constitution (Box 145)
    - Planning Materials, 1987 (Box 145, Folder F.1)
    - Promotional Packet, 1987 (Box 145, Folder F.2)
    - Draft of Program Introduction, undated (Box 145, Folder F.3)
    - Case I: "The President and Arms Control"--Transcript, undated (Box 145, Folder F.4)
    - Case II: "The President and the Judiciary"--Transcript, 1987 January 9, (3 Folders) (Box 145, Folder F.5-7)
  - The Presidency and the Constitution (Box 146)
    - Case III: "Proposed Changes in the Constitution," 1987 (Box 146, Folder F.1)
  - Profit and Promises: Reworking the American Dream --Seminar Report and Clippings, 1994 (Box 146, Folder F.2)
  - Problems of the Administration of Justice --Research Notes, 1990 (Box 146, Folder F.3)
  - Racism, undated (Box 146, Folder F.4)
  - Reading, Writing, and the Law --Transcripts, 1980, (2 Folders) (Box 146, Folder F.5-6)
  - Religion and the Law --Transcripts, 1983 (Box 146, Folder F.7)
  - Religion and the Law --Transcripts, 1983, (2 Folders) (Box 147, Folder F.1-2)
  - Right to Die? --Research Notes and Articles, 1989-1990, (2 Folders) (Box 147, Folder F.3-4)
  - The Role of the Media --Seminar Outline, 1992 (Box 147, Folder F.5)
  - Schools under Siege: Who Gives a Damn?-- Research Notes and Articles, 1990, (4 Folders) (Box 147, Folder F.6-9)
  - Schools under Siege --Transcript, 1990 October 29 (Box 148, Folder F.1)
  - Stakeholders: New Challenges in a Global Marketplace --Notes and Articles, 1990, (2 Folders) (Box 148, Folder F.2-3)
  - State of Television News --Transcript, 1986 November 25 (Box 148, Folder F.4)
  - Television and Terrorism --Production Materials, 1990, (2 Folders) (Box 148, Folder F.5-6)
  - Terrorism Retreat--Research Notes and Articles, 1986 (Folder F.7)
    - Production Materials, 1991, (2 Folders) (Box 149)
    - PBS Contract, 1991 (Box 149, Folder F.3)
    - Photographs for Promotional Booklet, 1991 (Box 149, Folder F.4)
    - Hypotheticals and Research Notes, 1991, (3 Folders) (Box 149, Folder F.5-7)
  - Theater of Learning--Proposal, 1984 (Box 150, Folder F.1)
  - Who Shall Be Healed? --Research Notes and Outline, 1992, (2 Folders) (Box 150, Folder F.2-3)
  - Who Lives, Who Dies? --Research Notes and Articles, circa 1991 (Box 150, Folder F.4)
  - Origins of Media and Society Seminars--Interview with Fred and Ruth Friendly, 1996 (Box 150, Folder F.5)
  - Clippings, 1984-1990 (Box 150, Folder F.6)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 150, Folder F.7)
  - Untitled Transcript Drafts, undated (Box 150, Folder F.8)
  - Hypotheticals, undated (Box 150, Folder F.9)
  - Annenberg/CPB Project (Production Company for Telecourses)--Reports and Correspondence, 1984-1994, (8 Folders) (Box 151, Folder F.1-8)
- Series IV: Conferences and Seminars, 1962-1996
  In addition to overseeing MSS, Friendly was also an active participant at government, business, and professional conferences. In some cases he was asked to replicate the round-table style of MSS at corporate retreats or annual meetings. At other events, he served as a moderator, panelist, or specialist. Files in this subseries contain notes, correspondence, and programs, and are arranged alphabetically by event title or topic. Two folders at the end of the subseries include invitations and programs for additional events.
  - 1st Circuit Judicial Conference, 1983 October 24 (Box 152, Folder F.1)
  - 2nd Circuit Judicial Conference, 1991 September 5 (Box 152, Folder F.2)
  - 9th Circuit Judicial Conference, 1986 August 17 (Box 152, Folder F.3)
  - The Abingdon Conference on Political Extremism, the Media and the Law, 1979 November 16 (Box 152, Folder F.4)
  - Advertising Association of Ft. Wayne, 1990 January 12 (Box 152, Folder F.5)
  - Advertising, News and the First Amendment, 1986 December 18 (Box 152, Folder F.6)
  - Advertising Women of NYC, 1989 (Box 152, Folder F.7)
  - An Agenda for the 1990 Health, Education, Welfare, 1988 April 12 (Box 152, Folder F.8)
  - Anatomy of a Company Move, 1987 (Box 152, Folder F.9)
  - Anatomy of a Development, 1988 (Box 152, Folder F.10)
  - Anatomy of Hate: Saving Our Children, 1992 (Box 152, Folder F.11)
  - Association of Independent Colleges (AICS), 1989 October 18-21 (Box 152, Folder F.12)
  - At the Heart of Our Care: Fulfilling Health Care's Social Responsibility, 1991 (Box 152, Folder F.13)
  - Seminar on Bilingualism and Education, 1987 (Box 153, Folder F.1)
  - The Bill of Rights: Our Guarantee of Freedom, 1990 (Box 153, Folder F.2)
  - Bill of Rights Forum, 1990 (Box 153, Folder F.3)
  - Bio-Ethics Seminar, 1992 (Box 153, Folder F.4)
  - Bold Initiatives for a New Era of Medicine: New Directions for Health Care Leadership, 1987 April 27-29 (Box 153, Folder F.5)
  - Broadcasting and the Constitution, 1987 July 13 (Box 153, Folder F.6)
  - Building a World Class Workforce, 1990 April 30 (Box 153, Folder F.7)
  - Business Forum, 1990 October (Box 153, Folder F.8)
  - Business, Journalism and Ethics, 1990 June 12 (Box 153, Folder F.9)
  - Campus Journalism, 1985 December 14 (Box 153, Folder F.10)
  - CASE Seminar, 1985 (Box 153, Folder F.11)
  - Center for Research and Development in Law-Related Education (CRADLE), 1992 (Box 153)
  - Change and Choice, 1987 February 11 (Box 153, Folder F.12)
  - Changes in Health Care, 1987 May 12 (Box 153, Folder F.13)
  - The Changing Advertiser/Agency Relationship, 1988 May 18 (Box 154, Folder F.1)
  - Citicorp Program, 1989 (Box 154, Folder F.2)
  - Civility and Civil Rights on Campus, 1991 October 3 (Box 154, Folder F.3)
  - Cold War Retrospective: Did We Get the Story Right? 1990 March 17 (Box 154, Folder F.4)
  - Columbia University Alumni Club, 1987 April 23 (Box 154, Folder F.5)
  - Communications Law Explosion, 1973 November 1-2 (Box 154, Folder F.6)
  - Confluence: Source of New Energy --Medical Library Association, 1987 May 15-20 (Box 154, Folder F.7)
  - The Constitution, 1987, (2 Folders) (Box 154, Folder F.8-9)
  - Corporate Governance: The Voice of the Shareholder in the Control of the Company, 1990 November 12 (Box 154, Folder F.10)
  - Corporate Takeovers: Ethics and the Law, 1990 March 15 (Box 154, Folder F.11)
  - Corpus Christi Education Summit, 1990 February 27 (Box 154, Folder F.12)
  - Corpus Christi Education Summit, 1990 February 27 (Box 155, Folder F.1)
  - Courage and Ethics in the News: Following the Murrow Tradition, 1989 April 10 (Box 155, Folder F.2)
  - The Courts, the Media, and the Public, 1989 May 23 (Box 155, Folder F.3)
  - The Creative Executive, 1986 November 10 (Box 155, Folder F.4)
  - Crime in America, 1987 March 1 (Box 155, Folder F.5)
  - Crossroads of Humanity, 1993 June 12 (Box 155, Folder F.6)
  - Dangerous Ideas, 1989 October 8 (Box 155, Folder F.7)
  - Deans Distinguished Lectures, 1991 (Box 155, Folder F.8)
  - Decriminalization of Drugs, 1990 May 5 (Box 155, Folder F.9)
  - The Deficit and the Constitution, 1986 March 16 (Box 155, Folder F.10)
  - Dialogue on Employment Training, 1988 September 26 (Box 155, Folder F.11)
  - Doctors and Lawyers at the Crossroads, 1988 March 18 (Box 155, Folder F.12)
  - Docudrama: Why Is It Controversial? 1986 April 4 (Box 155, Folder F.13)
  - Doctors and Lawyers at the Crossroads, 1988 March 18 (Box 155, Folder F.14)
  - Drinking Water Technology and Ethics, 1987 March 14 (Box 155, Folder F.15)
  - Due Process/First Amendment, 1988 May 14 (Box 156, Folder F.1)
  - Earth 2020 Rethinking Our Relationship to the Environment, 1990 April 19 (Box 156, Folder F.2)
  - Eastern Educational Consortium Conference, 1988 October 26 (Box 156, Folder F.3)
  - Economic Summit, 1990 July 9 (Box 156, Folder F.4)
  - Th e Editorial Integrity Project, 1986 January 20 (Box 156, Folder F.5)
  - Education 2015 Strategies for a Humane, Peaceful and Equitable World, 1987 (Box 156, Folder F.6)
  - Education: Issues Facing American Business, 1990 April 11 (Box 156, Folder F.7)
  - Education and the Media: Are Graduates Meeting Broadcast Needs? 1989 November 11 (Box 156, Folder F.8)
  - Educational Resources and Equity: Who Takes the Cuts? 1991 March 15 (Box 156, Folder F.9)
  - Educational Seminar, 1990 September 14 (Box 156, Folder F.10)
  - Ethical and Constitutional Issues Facing Journalists, 1988 September 16 (Box 156, Folder F.11)
  - Ethical Issues, 1988 October 14 (Box 156, Folder F.12)
  - Ethical Management Standards, 1991 June 7 (Box 156, Folder F.13)
  - Ethics Forum, Dartmouth, 1988 (Box 156, Folder F.14)
  - Ethics and Health Care, 1986 October 17 (Box 157, Folder F.1)
  - Ethics and Legislation, 1986 (Box 157, Folder F.2)
  - Ethics and Litigation: Changing Rules of the Road, 1986 August 12 (Box 157, Folder F.3)
  - Ethics and Marketing, 1986 October 15 (Box 157, Folder F.4)
  - Ethics and Values in Today's Society, 1986 October 29 (Box 157, Folder F.5)
  - Ethics in American Education, 1989 December 1 (Box 157, Folder F.6)
  - Ethics in American Public Life, 1988 February 29 (Box 157, Folder F.7)
  - Ethics in Business: the Hard Choices, 1989 May 17 (Box 157, Folder F.8)
  - Ethics in the Law and Media, 1989 March 7 (Box 157, Folder F.9)
  - Ethics in the Media, 1991 April 11 (Box 157, Folder F.10)
  - Ethics, Provosts Forum, 1990 April 18 (Box 157, Folder F.11)
  - Ethics Seminars--Programs, 1988-1990 (Box 157, Folder F.12)
  - Exploring the Philosophical, circa 1988 (Box 157, Folder F.13)
  - The Fallout From Chernobyl, 1989 February 11 (Box 158, Folder F.1)
  - Fashion Institute of Technology, 1985 (Box 158, Folder F.2)
  - The Federal Judiciary: What Role Politics? 1985 February 16 (Box 158, Folder F.3)
  - Financial World, 1989 September 13 (Box 158, Folder F.4)
  - First Amendment Seminars, 1985-1991 (Box 158, Folder F.5)
  - First Family Life, 1992 October 15 (Box 158, Folder F.6)
  - Fox Broadcasting Television Critics Panel, 1991 August 5 (Box 158, Folder F.7)
  - Free Expression After 200 Years, 1991 March 4 (Box 158, Folder F.8)
  - Free Trial, Fair Press, 1987 February 19, (2 Folders) (Box 158, Folder F.9-10)
  - Frontier Thinking: Sustaining Environment, Protecting Development, 1990 March 21 (Box 158, Folder F.11)
  - The Future of Health Care in America, 1987 April 10 (Box 158, Folder F.12)
  - Future of Science and Services, 1990 October 23 (Box 158, Folder F.13)
  - Get the Feds Out of Higher Education, 1982 May 10 (Box 159, Folder F.1)
  - Government Computers, 1989 (Box 159, Folder F.2)
  - Government Structure, undated (Box 159, Folder F.3)
  - Health Aspects of Nuclear Power Plant Incidents, 1983 April 7 (Box 159, Folder F.4)
  - Health, Education, Welfare, 1987 April 12 (Box 159, Folder F.5)
  - Healthcare for the Aging, 1987 June 18 (Box 159, Folder F.6)
  - Healthcare in America: Change, Challenge and Controversy, 1987 November 10 (Box 159, Folder F.7)
  - Honor Medical Society, 1991 November 21 (Box 159, Folder F.8)
  - Hospitals and the Elderly, 1987 March 12 (Box 159, Folder F.9)
  - Hospital Trustee Forum, 1991 October 5 (Box 159, Folder F.10)
  - Seminar on Hostage Situations, 1990 (Box 159, Folder F.11)
  - Impact Symposium, 1989 February 16 (Box 159, Folder F.12)
  - The Impact of the Media on Political Institutions, 1985 August 8 (Box 159, Folder F.13)
  - In the Interests of Justice --Transcript, 1985 October 28 (Box 159, Folder F.14)
  - In Pursuit of Useful Knowledge: Journalists as Educators, 1989 (Box 159, Folder F.15)
  - Industrial Development Research Council, 1990 October 31 (Box 159, Folder F.16)
  - Independent Filmmaker's Association, 1983 April 10 (Box 159, Folder F.17)
  - Institute for Retired Professionals, 1993 (Box 159, Folder F.18)
  - Integration: Success Through Teamwork, 1988 May 25 (Box 159, Folder F.19)
  - International Radio Television Foundation Dinner, 1991 (Box 159, Folder F.20)
  - Ivy Plus News--Director's Conference, 1990 (Box 159, Folder F.21)
  - John Peter Zenger: A Symposium, 1985 October 25 (Box 160, Folder F.1)
  - Judges, Journalism and the Constitution, 1985 April 19 (Box 160, Folder F.2)
  - Judicature, 1982 June 10 (Box 160, Folder F.3)
  - Kidspeak Forum, 1988 March 12 (Box 160, Folder F.4)
  - Law Day, 1990 May 3 (Box 160, Folder F.5)
  - Libel Defense Resource Center Jury Project, 1983 November 17 (Folder F.6)
    - "The Price of Politics," 1996 December 14 (Box 160)
    - "Whose Law, Whose Order?" 1996 December 14 (Box 160, Folder F.8)
    - "Privacy and Security on the Eve of the Millennium," 1996 December 15 (Box 160, Folder F.9)
  - The Mandate to Broaden, 1991 October 12 (Box 160, Folder F.10)
  - The Mass Communications Explosion Legacy of the 20th Century, 1989 February 2 (Box 160, Folder F.11)
  - Media: Behind the Headlines, 1984 February 15 (Box 160, Folder F.12)
  - The Media and Children's Issues, 1985 November 26 (Box 160, Folder F.13)
  - Media Ethics and Privacy, 1989 October 2 (Box 160, Folder F.14)
  - Media Executive Conference, 1989 (Box 160, Folder F.15)
  - The Media and the Information Industry, 1986 April 29 (Box 160, Folder F.16)
  - Media and the Law, 1979 (Box 160, Folder F.17)
  - The Media: Perils and Promise, 1990 March 24 (Box 161, Folder F.1)
  - Media, Power and Democracy, 1987 May 15 (Box 161, Folder F.2)
  - Media Standards and Journalistic Accountability, 1989 March 23 (Box 161, Folder F.3)
  - Medical Ethics--Transcript, 1980 (Box 161, Folder F.4)
  - Media Ethics and Privacy, 1989 October 2 (Box 161, Folder F.5)
  - Medical Malpractice, Ethics and the News Media, 1985 July 28 (Box 161, Folder F.6)
  - Mental Illness and the Media: The Next Step, 1988 October 20 (Box 161, Folder F.7)
  - Money and the University, 1990 (Box 161, Folder F.8)
  - Moral Issues in Managing Health Care, 1987 April 27 (Box 161, Folder F.9)
  - Murrow Symposium, 1983 (Box 161, Folder F.10)
  - National Business Leadership Conference, 1991 April 18 (Box 161, Folder F.11)
  - National Defense University Board of Visitors Meeting, 1985 (Box 161, Folder F.12)
  - Near vs. Minnesota: 50 Years Later, 1983 (Box 161, Folder F.13)
  - The New Agendas: A Regional Leadership Conference, 1989 January 13 (Box 161, Folder F.14)
  - The New Chief Executive, 1987 (Box 161, Folder F.15)
  - New Horizons: Probing the Next Decade, 1988 September 30 (Box 161, Folder F.16)
  - Seminar on New York City Campaign Finance, 1983 October 22 (Box 162, Folder F.1)
  - New Jersey Bar Bicentennial, 1987 (Box 162, Folder F.2)
  - New York Partnership Meeting, 1991 June 25 (Box 162, Folder F.3)
  - New York Governance in the 21st Century: A Public-Private Partnership, 1988 (Box 162, Folder F.4)
  - New York State Juvenile Justice System, 1985 November 23 (Box 162, Folder F.5)
  - Newspaper Publishing Seminar, 1989 March 5 (Box 162, Folder F.6)
  - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York, 1987 December 8 (Box 162, Folder F.7)
  - Northern Justice Conference and Alaskan Bar Association Convention, 1990 June 7-9 (Box 162, Folder F.8)
  - Nursing Homes, 1988 October 18 (Box 162, Folder F.9)
  - The Police and the Public, 1982 May 7 (Box 162, Folder F.10)
  - Politics and the Mass Media, 1970 (Box 162, Folder F.11)
  - Preserving the Global Environment: The Challenge of Shared Leadership, 1990 April 19 (Box 162, Folder F.12)
  - The Presidency, 1983 (Box 162, Folder F.13)
  - Press and the Public: The Right to Know, 1988 October 24 (Box 162, Folder F.14)
  - The Press, the Constitution and Responsibility, 1987 April 2 (Box 162, Folder F.15)
  - Press Panel Discussion, 1983 January 28 (Box 162, Folder F.16)
  - The Press Today: Free and Fair? 1986 March 8 (Box 162, Folder F.17)
  - Privacy, News, and the First Amendment, 1989 (Box 163, Folder F.1)
  - Privacy vs. the Right to Know: HIV Testing in Health Care, 1991 November (Box 163, Folder F.2)
  - Problems of the Administration of Justice and Law Enforcement in the North, 1990 June 7 (Box 163, Folder F.3)
  - Program in Applied Ethics, 1989 March 28 (Box 163, Folder F.4)
  - Provosts Forum, Kent State University, 1990 April 18 (Box 163, Folder F.5)
  - Public Association Library Program, 1989 (Box 163, Folder F.6)
  - The Public is Right, 1989 February 7 (Box 163, Folder F.7)